looknbook.com 2012-12-31

# www.looknbook.com

##  Privacy Policy

is a wholly owned subsidiary of Spring Travels (P) Ltd.

is committed to protecting our customer’s privacy. We employ the highest levels of security to keep the personal information of our valued customers strictly confidential. We will not disclose or sell any of your personal information, including your name, address, credit card details or transaction history to any third party without your permission. We do not use cookies

As you are our registered member of , you will be entitled to savings and benefits on airfares, hotel reservations, holiday packages, among other travel services. In addition, look forward to receiving our newsletters & promotions offering special deals.

In general, you can visit  website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze the data for statistics, but your information remains anonymous.

Some of our web pages use "cookies" so that we can better serve you with customized information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you.

will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share on our website. We have implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure. You should access our privacy policy regularly to ensure you understand our current policies. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line.  will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt.

When you register with , we or any of our partners/affiliate/group companies may contact you from time to time to provide the offers/information of such products/services that we believe may benefit you.
